<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cross Country Evangelism Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://crosscountryevangelism.com/newsletter.html</link>
    <description>Quarterly updates from Cross Country Evangelism.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2025 Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://crosscountryevangelism.com/newsletters/2025-12.html</link>
      <guid>https://crosscountryevangelism.com/newsletters/2025-12.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>September-December 2025: ministry updates and photo highlights from NYC, Massachusetts, Ohio, and Virginia.</description>
      <media:content url="https://crosscountryevangelism.com/images/NL-2025-12-01.jpg" medium="image" />
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://crosscountryevangelism.com/newsletters/2025-12.html">View this newsletter on the web.</a></p>
<div>
  <strong>Share:</strong>
  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/sharer/sharer.php?u=https%3A%2F%2Fcrosscountryevangelism.com%2Fnewsletters%2F2025-12.html">Facebook</a>
  <a href="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcrosscountryevangelism.com%2Fnewsletters%2F2025-12.html&text=Fall%202025%20Newsletter">X</a>
  <a href="mailto:?subject=Fall%202025%20Newsletter&body=https%3A%2F%2Fcrosscountryevangelism.com%2Fnewsletters%2F2025-12.html">Email</a>
</div>
<h2>Fall 2025 Newsletter</h2>
<p><strong>September-December 2025</strong></p>
<p>Thank you for praying for Cross Country Evangelism. Here are the latest ministry updates and photo highlights from our fall travels.</p>
<h3>New York City Outreach</h3>
<p>It has been a great few months for Cross Country Evangelism. We have traveled to the Northeast, the Midwest, and the Southeast with the gospel. We participated with ATL's Voice in NYC for the week of September 11th. Jason Cantrell has been inviting evangelists to open air preach with him around the city for the week culminating with a gospel outreach at Ground Zero. We heralded the truth and interacted with many people throughout the city, on the subway, the Staten Island Ferry, Battery Park, Time Square, Union Square, and Washington Square Park. We even spent a day preaching at the infamous Planned Parenthood in Manhattan on Bleeker Street which is now permanently closed. Going to the Big Apple gives the opportunity to share the gospel with people from all over the world who are always willing to stop and dialogue.</p>
<h3>Massachusetts Campus Outreach</h3>
<p>The last week of October we teamed with some saints in Massachusetts to labor at a few college campuses; Salem State University, the University of Connecticut, and UMass Lowell. Overall, the students at the schools in Massachusetts were quite beside themselves, yet it is to be expected at those two institutions. At Salem State we were greeted with a rough LGBTQ reception with some of the students spouting tolerance yet showing their intolerance towards the gospel message. The students at UMass Lowell provided a very similar reception with one student throwing milk on one of the preachers and was quickly arrested for disorderly behavior and another student stole a sign and was apprehended by the police shortly afterwards as well. There was even an article in the school paper about the outreach that day. Despite the foolishness and folly, the Good News still went forward to the many students and facility at the institutions for the glory of King Jesus. By God's grace the Christian students on those campuses were very encouraged we came to take a stand for Christ, and some were compelled to share the gospel with their classmates while we were there and they engaged us with questions about being better at evangelism, they received and provided prayer and shared their testimonies. We finished our time in the state with an outreach on the streets of Salem, MA on Halloween. People come from all over the world for the holiday celebration and it affords a great opportunity to proclaim the gospel to tens of thousands of people, young and old in the center of the city well into the evening.</p>
<h3>Ohio Ministry Stops</h3>
<p>We visited with the saints in Ohio at LaRue Baptist Church, Providence Church, and Redeemer Covenant Church. We were able to do ministry at Cleveland State University with pastors Austin Hetsler and Ralph Hull and gave away many gospel tracts and preached the gospel to throngs of people in the thousands and gave away hundreds of tracts before the Ohio State University football game against the team from Rutgers with our dear brother Michael Coughlin.</p>
<h3>Virginia in December</h3>
<p>The first weekend in December we traveled to Hampton, VA to meet with Don "Stonewall" Karns and present the Good News at the Dominion Energy Christmas Parade in Richmond, VA. It is a great venue; the people are attentive and mostly take the tracts and some even applaud when the preaching is done. Later in the afternoon we took the gospel to Colonial Williamsburg where the street and sidewalks are filled with many families and shoppers who come for the Grand Illumination Fireworks. It is a great opportunity to give witness of the Lord Jesus Christ during the Christmas Season.</p>
<h3>Prayer and Travel Notes</h3>
<p>In Salem, Mike has had an ongoing interaction over the years with a transvestite whom he has been trying to win to Christ. He seems like hard ground, however Mike continues to pray for his salvation. This year in direct answer to prayer the Lord enabled a little bit longer of a conversation between them than the two have had in the past. In October Robert traveled to London with Sports Fans Outreach International for gospel preaching throughout the city of London during the week and for two NFL football games at massive venues. He also labored with Phil Close and Jimmy Hamilton in their respective "fishing holes" in the Birmingham and Nottingham area in the UK. In November Mike attended the Men's Summit Meeting with Christ The Rock Church in Ohio and was edified by the messages and fellowship that went on there.</p>
<p>Next, we travel to Jamacia with a small team for our sixteenth trip to the island. Please keep us in prayer as we go the herald the glorious gospel of Jesus Christ!</p>
<h3>Photo Highlights</h3>
<p>
  <a href="https://crosscountryevangelism.com/images/NL-2025-12-01.jpg">
    <img src="https://crosscountryevangelism.com/images/NL-2025-12-01.jpg" alt="Cross Country Evangelism outreach highlights." />
  </a>
</p>
<p>
  <a href="https://crosscountryevangelism.com/images/NL-2025-12-02.jpg">
    <img src="https://crosscountryevangelism.com/images/NL-2025-12-02.jpg" alt="Cross Country Evangelism outreach highlights." />
  </a>
</p>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
